Contact

sanchezronney@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ronney-sanchez-20a263146 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Manufacturing
Microsoft Office
Customer Service

Ronney Sanchez

Machine Operator at MilliporeSigma

Lawrence, Massachusetts, United States

Summary

I enrolled at UMASS Lowell to study Computer Science. I have experience with C/C++, Java, HTML, CSS, Python, and JavaScript. In JAVA, I used the Unified Modeling Language, as known as the UML diagram, to create member variables, and methods within a class and instantiate into objects. In C++ I used the Simple and Fast Multimedia Library to create program animations in a window screen.

Experience

MilliporeSigma
Machine Operator
June 2022 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Danvers, Massachusetts, United States

Cell Coordinator

Automatic Port Bonder

Manual Port Bonder

Leak (Integrity) Testing

Make Bags

Forming interchangeable parts together to form an end product

Randstad USA

Machine Operator

September 2021 - June 2022 (10 months)

United States

Make bags

Manual Port Bonder

Automatic Port Bonder

Forming interchangeable parts together for an end product

Demoulas Super Markets, Inc.

7 years 4 months

Produce Clerk

August 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 2 months)

Page 1 of 2

United States

Sacker

June 2014 - August 2020 (6 years 3 months) United States

Education

University of Massachusetts Lowell

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2018 - 2019)

Northern Essex Community College
Associate of Science - AS, Computer and Information Sciences,
General · (2015 - 2017)

Lawrence High School High School Diploma · (2010 - 2014)